Jeez.
If you were done with work,
you could've just asked me to come over.
Hey.
Hey...
You were taking forever to call me,
so I just came over myself.
I even picked up some food on the way.
Hey...
You must be dying to hold me by now, right?
Well...
Takaaki, I'm starving.
Let's eat the bento I bought.
Okay.
Pepper steak or ginger pork.
Which one do you want?
You pick your favorite, Naoya.
Then I'll take the ginger pork.
Sorry.
I can never cook for you.
I don't have anything here.
It's fine.
You're always busy with work, right?
By the way,
Have you been eating properly?
I guess so.
Whenever you come over,
you always make me super healthy meals.
You should take better
care of yourself, too.
If you collapse from exhaustion,
I'd be in a lot of trouble.
Oh, right.
Want me to help you check
those documents after we eat?
I have tomorrow off anyway.
Sure, I'd appreciate that.
No problem. Leave it to me.
But man,
this workload is insane.
You're handling all this by yourself?
I'm so glad you're helping me out.
I have no idea how you managed to
come to my place three times a week before.
Hey,
should I just move in here?
Huh?
"The Servant Prince"
(Episode 6)
Should I just move in here?
Huh?
Takaaki, you were the one who got that room
for me when I was completely broke, right?
If I cancel that lease and stay here,
I can help out with the living expenses.
It would lighten your
burden a bit, wouldn't it?
Plus,
it'd be much easier for us
to find time to see each other.
Huh?
Takaaki?
What?
This is...
After selling the
apartment under your name,
and paying off the remaining mortgage, there
was still a substantial amount left over.
I actually could have gotten you
something much better than a studio.
But ever since we were young, whenever you felt
vulnerable, you liked to hide in small spaces.
That's right...
Just like how you used to curl up on the
sofa in the dimly lit computer club room.
A little box where you could heal.
A secret place
that only I knew about.
I was planning to give this to you
once you were back on your feet.
You can use this money
as capital to start a business.
Or you could buy a new apartment.
You don't need to worry at all
about being a burden to me.
Sorry for keeping this from you.
Heh.
Looks like that apartment was worth
a lot more than I thought.
It's fine.
If you had given me that money back then,
it definitely wouldn't have ended well.
Yeah.
The rhythmic sound of typing
and Takaaki's back.
It's been like this for a long time.
I'll think about it.
But until then,
can I still come over like this?
Forget about the place or being a burden.
I just want to see you more.
The thing that heals me the most
is always being by your side.
I was so lonely not seeing you for so long.
What's with that look?
You've been really cute lately.
You're welcome here anytime.
Thanks.
[Some kind of dossier on Takaaki
including his performance as a young CEO)
Excuse me.
President.
We got a reply from Unicolab
regarding the contract.
Hmph. With the amount we offered, they
must be wagging their tails in acceptance.
No, they formally declined.
What?
We made so many concessions.
What's the meaning of this?
It doesn't seem to be
an issue with the quote.
Anyway, they said it's unacceptable.
Excuse me, President.
Yuma, what is it?
Regarding the bidding for the
station-front development project,
are we really moving forward like this?
Obviously.
I'm busy.
Don't come running to
me for every little thing.
I'm very sorry.
I'll take my leave.
Good morning.
Oh, Goto-kun.
- You're early today.
- Yes.
Huh?
Is this a new dessert?
Yeah, I thought I'd try
changing the pancake mix.
I used rice flour this time.
It's what they call gluten-free.
I see.
Smells great.
- Looks delicious.
- Right?
By the way, Goto-kun,
if you don't mind,
want to give it a taste?
Oh, can I?
Of course.
It's delicious.
It's really chewy.
I actually prefer this one.
Really?
That's great.
This is really nice.
To think the head chef can
make something like this.
Come on, I've been a pro
in this industry for thirty years.
Thirty years, huh?
I'm twenty-seven now,
so that's longer than I've been alive.
Hey, hold on a second.
Are you calling me an old man?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I'm just kidding.
If you want to learn,
I can teach you the recipe.
It's actually pretty simple.
You can easily make it at home.
Really?
Of course.
You're pretty handy.
Do you cook often?
No, not at all.
Really? I couldn't tell.
You must be good with your hands.
You're probably great at everything.
Not at all.
Don't be modest.
The manager and Mori-san said so, too.
They said even though you have no customer
service experience, you're incredibly adaptable.
And you handle complaints flawlessly.
That's because...
I guess a nepo baby
is just useless after all.
Ruining your family's company.
You're completely worthless.
You have zero management skills.
You're an absolute disaster.
Because I used to be surrounded
by much worse people.
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
It's done, it's done.
Oh, I see.
See? Pretty simple, right?
Yes.
Of course, we tweak it a bit for the store.
Like adding some whipped cream or fruit.
The rest is just professional technique.
Makes sense.
Anyway, that's the basic method.
Thank you.
I'll definitely give it a try.
By the way, who are you
learning to make this for?
Ah...
- For a friend.
- A friend?
Excuse me.
President.
I've brought him.
Long time no see,
President Goto.
Thank you for always
looking after my father.
I've already heard the gist of your visit
from your secretary, Tanizawa-san.
If it's about Unicolab,
please leave it to me.
Their president, Sato Takaaki,
is a former classmate of mine.
(I'm heading to the supermarket
first, I'll be over in a bit.)
It really is Naoya.
This guy...
That's Naoya for you.
With Naoya here, we're definitely
winning the sports tournament.
I'll follow you for life.
We're counting on you.
Back in high school,
he was one of my lackeys, I think.
What a surprise.
I heard you hit rock bottom, but...
I never imagined
you'd be running errands
for that four-eyes now.
I've heard quite a bit.
Want me to put in a good word
and get you back into the company?
Get in.
You look pathetic.
Dressed like a total bottom-feeder.
So?
Who told you to come here?
Are you deaf?
I'm asking whose orders you're following.
You bastard.
Watch your attitude.
You think you have the
right to question me?
If you think I'm still the same as before,
you're dead wrong.
I've been sick of you since back then.
You're nothing but a guy who got
lucky being born as the president's son.
Whatever.
You must know about the data leak
at Goto Construction, right?
When I heard that four-eyes'
company was handling the security,
I was actually pretty shocked.
That guy...
Even though he bailed halfway through,
we offered him a great deal to re-sign,
but he still wouldn't agree to it.
Your dad hasn't said anything publicly,
but it seems to be a real headache for him.
So I figured I'd step in as a mediator
and get things moving.
Oh.
Running into you here must be fate.
I might as well do you a favor, too.
So watch your mouth.
Why is it that the people around my father
always talk like this?
There's a meeting here tonight.
Wait in the lobby.
Am I too dressed-down for the moment?
Sorry about that.
Well, we should probably get going.
Okay.
Say bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye.
- See you next time.
- Have a safe trip home.
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Come with me.
(I'm going to the supermarket
first. I'll head over to your place later.)
He's still not back.
The number you dialed
is currently unavailable.
I'll give you five minutes.
If you get on your knees and apologize,
I'll forgive you.
All you have to do is say,
"I can't do it," and bow your head to Dad.
He'll give you whatever position you want.
Come back.
I can't hold on much longer all by myself.
I refuse.
I have no intention of ever going back.
That's what I came here to tell you.
You're getting more and
more like your mother.
You're going to regret this.
The number you dialed
is currently unavailable.
(Next Episode Preview)
What are you doing?
Crap.
Stop it, Takaaki!
I have some exclusive
information about your son.
So you guys are in this together?
We'll be living here starting today.
Just the two of us.